<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="100">
    <author>Ritter</author>
    <version>0.3.4.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Adjust Storage Capacity</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Need more room in your silos or trailers? Or want to limit storage to make gameplay more challenging?

Adjust Storage Capacity lets you customize storage capacities for silos, production facilities, animal husbandries, and vehicles. Whether you want massive storage for convenience or reduced capacity for a realistic challenge, you can set any value without editing XML files.

Supports multiplayer with permission system - admins can modify any storage, farm managers can modify their own farm's storage.

Features:
- Press K near any supported storage or vehicle to open capacity dialog
- Press K in Production or Animals menu to adjust selected facility
- Edit capacity for each fill type or fill unit
- Capacity protection: clamps to fill level to prevent data loss
- Configurable key binding for opening dialogs
- Multiplayer support with permissions

Supported:
- Silos, tanks, warehouses
- Production storage
- Husbandry input/output (straw, water, milk, manure)
- Animal food troughs
- Vehicle fill units (trailers, harvesters, sprayers, tankers)

Not Supported:
- Bunker silos (terrain heap-based)
- Pallets and bales (object storage)
- Vehicle pallets and big bags (products, not containers)
- Leveler fill units (internal buffers)

Console commands available.

Changelog:
0.3.4.0 (Alpha):
- Fixed K keybind for placeables getting stuck when entering vehicles

0.3.3.0 (Alpha):
- Fixed fill levels being lost when loading savegames with expanded capacity

0.3.2.0 (Alpha):
- Added capacity protection: clamps to fill level to prevent data loss
- Fixed K keybind getting stuck when entering/exiting vehicles
- Added permission blocking for NPC farm and spectator assets
- Console lists now show only assets you have permission to modify
- Fixed multiplayer sync corruption when adjusting animal food trough capacity

0.3.1.0 (Alpha):
- Fixed K keybind conflict when near both placeable and vehicle

0.3.0.0 (Alpha):
- Added vehicle capacity adjustment (trailers, harvesters, etc.)
- Walk near any vehicle with fill units to press K and adjust
- Console commands for vehicles

0.2.0.0 (Alpha):
- Added K button to Production and Animals in-game menus
- Adjust capacity directly from menu without approaching storage
- Fixed dialog overlay issue (now properly covers menu background)

0.1.0.0:
- Initial alpha release
- GUI dialog for viewing and editing storage capacities
- Inline editing with double-click or Enter
- Full multiplayer support with permissions
- Console commands for advanced users

Documentation: https://github.com/rittermod/FS25_AdjustStorageCapacity
        ]]>        </en>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon_adjustStorageCapacity.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <!-- External localization files -->
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="RM_ADJUST_STORAGE_CAPACITY"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="RM_ADJUST_STORAGE_CAPACITY">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_k"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
