<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="106">
    <author>Ritter</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Adjust Storage Capacity</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Need more room in your silos or trailers? Or want to limit storage to make gameplay more challenging?

Adjust Storage Capacity lets you customize storage capacities for silos, production facilities, animal husbandries, and vehicles. Adjust from anywhere - approach a facility, open in-game menus, or press K while driving to adjust your vehicle and implements on the go. Set any value without editing XML files.

Optional auto-scale settings keep expanded vehicles drivable by adjusting mass and load/discharge speed proportionally.

Supports multiplayer with permission system.

Features:
- Press K near any supported storage or vehicle to open capacity dialog
- Press K while driving to adjust your vehicle and attached implements
- Press K in Production, Animals, Workshop, or Construction menus
- Edit capacity for each fill type or fill unit
- "Reset All" button to restore original capacities
- Capacity protection: clamps to fill level to prevent data loss
- Auto-scale vehicle mass and load/discharge speed (optional)
- Optional setting to hide trigger shortcuts (menu access always available)
- Configurable key binding
- Multiplayer support with permissions

Supported:
- Silos, tanks, warehouses
- Production storage
- Husbandry input/output (straw, water, milk, manure)
- Animal food troughs
- Vehicle fill units (trailers, harvesters, sprayers, tankers)

Not Supported:
- Bunker silos (terrain heap-based)
- Pallets and bales (object storage)
- Vehicle pallets and big bags (products, not containers)
- Leveler fill units (internal buffers)

Changelog:

1.0.0.0:
- Fixed 3D fill visuals (vehicle heaps, food troughs) not showing correctly after loading a savegame
- Fixed straw bedding and water visuals not updating when capacity is changed
- Fixed 3D fill plane rendering issues in silos and food troughs

0.6.1.0 (Beta):
- Fixed excess fill not being removed when resetting capacity to original (shared capacity storages reduce proportionally)
- Fixed reset failing on newly placed buildings with "No original capacities recorded" error

Documentation: https://github.com/rittermod/FS25_AdjustStorageCapacity
        ]]>        </en>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon_adjustStorageCapacity.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <!-- External localization files -->
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="RM_ADJUST_STORAGE_CAPACITY"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="RM_ADJUST_STORAGE_CAPACITY">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_k"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
